pandafreegames.in 2015-12-26

# Privacy Policy - Panda Free games

**This Privacy Policy is the same for the domains:**

pandafreegames.net ; pandafreegames.com ; pandafreegames.ie ; pandafreegames.co.uk ; pandafreegames.ca ; pandafreegames.in ; pandafreegames.com.pk ; pandafreegames.co.za ; pandafreegames.com.my ; pandafreegames.com.au ; pandafreegames.com.ph ; pandafreegames.co.nz ; pandafreegames.sg ; pandafreegames.com.ng ; pandafreegames.co.ke

**Privacy Policy Panda Free Games**

Quick overview: we are using cookies to give you the best experience on our site. Cookies are used by most websites to help personalise your web experience. By continuing to use our website, these will always be active.

If you need any more information or have questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by pandagamesweb@gmail.com   
At www.pandafreegames.net, the privacy of our visitors is extreme important to us. This privacy policy text outlines explain the types of personal information is received and collected by us (www.pandafreegames.net) and how it is used for us and third parts.

**Log Files**

Like many other websites, www.pandafreegames.net use log files. This information inside the log files includes IP (internet protocol) address, type of browser (like Chrome, Firefox, Safari, Internet Explorer), Internet Service Provider (ISP), date & time stamp, referring or exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze statistics, administer the website, track users movement around this website, and gather demographic information, Country or city. IP addresses, and other such information are not associated to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies & Web Beacons**

www.pandafreegames.net use cookies to store some information about users/visitors preferences, record user-specific information’s on which pages the user visito r access, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type and compute ror mobile device or other information that the visitor sends by their browser. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our website www.pandafreegames.net.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to www.pandafreegames.net and other sites on our website and others on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> .  
Some of our advertising partners like Google may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Google adsense is one of our advertising partners.

These third-party ad servers/networks use technologies to the advertisements and links that appear on www.pandafreegames.net send directly to your browser. This technologies automatically receive your IP address when this happen. Other technologies (such cookies, JavaScript and Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements or to personalize their advertising content that you will see.   
www.pandafreegames.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by those third-party advertisers.   
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers like <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out certain practices.  
www.pandafreegames.net privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control this activities of, such other advertisers or other websites.   
If you wish to disable this cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about this cookies management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' websites or you can use other technologies like AD Block <https://adblockplus.org/> but as we said, this may affect the functionality of the website.
